Make it in Time, Nobita! The Robot Court
All done at last.
Too bad, Nobita-kun totally forgot to water the plants.
I've to write my observation notes.
It must be hard on you, Dora-chan!
Nobita relies on you too much.
Well, I'm used to it.
IS it my imagination or have you actually became little slimmer?
Hmm, you think so?
Doraemon!
Hey, Doraemon, lend me that gadget!
Welcome home!
Pull it out fast!
Why don't you say welcome home? Have you forget the aesthetics, Nobita?
But I'm in a hurry!
Lend me the Substitute Bag!
What are you gonna use it for?
I forgot and left my Schoolbag at school.
Unbeliveable, you forgot your school bag?
Dora-chan, you don't have to help him!
How pathetic!
Hey Doraemon, please!
It's so like you, Nobita-kun.
Here!
This is the Time Cloth!
Found it!
Got it! Thanks!
Help me clean up the mess, Nobita-kun...
He wouldn't, of course!
I'm not feeling good.
It feels like I have a fever.
Doraemon!
He's not in, huh?
Ah, so there you are!
Hey, Doraemon!
But you see, Nobita-kun...
I'm not feeling wel-...
'Kay, will be back in a while!
I'll contact Dorami, just in case!
Hello, what's up, Bro?!
Bro!
Hey, Bro!
Bro, you called me?
Oh, my?
Bro!
What happened?
Bro! Bro!
Wake up!
Oh no, he isn't waking up.
I've to call an ambulance.
You're doing so good!
I had lot of fun!
Nobita-san, welcome home!
Bro is feeling sick, so he's being treated at 22nd century robot hospital.
Please don't worry...
...also don't forget to do your homework.
Bye!
Dorameon is sick, huh?
Doraemon must have over ate Dorayaki.
Well, he's a glutton, after all.
Wake up!
You're Nobi Nobita-san, correct?
Y-yes, but who're you guys?
Robot Cops from the 22nd Century.
You will be put arrested under the act.
You're gonna arrest me?
That is correct, your friend Doraemon was hospitalised.
You have to submit yourself at the 22nd Century Robot Court.
At the court?
All right, take him.
Don't wanna! Hey, stop!
Don't wanna!
This must be some kind of a mistake!
Doraemon!
Nobita-san!
Grandpa!
Dorami-chan! Sewashi-kun!
Grandpa, this must be some kind of a mistake!
I'll be your attorney general, Nobita-san!
How's Doraemon?
Bro is just over-exhausted a little.
During our time at court...
Mini-Dora will keep us updated with Bro's health.
The trial will begin shortly.
Chief Justice
Defendant
The Robot Trials shall begin shortly.